{"flashcards":[{"id":1,"subject":"Maths","front":"What is the integral of cosxdx","back":"sinx","date_of_creation":"Sun Feb 05 2023 11:05:36 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":2,"subject":"Physics","date_of_creation":"Mon Feb 20 2023 15:30:05 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)","front":"What is the moment of inertia of a disk","back":"1/2mR^2 where R is the radius of the disk and m is the mass of the disk"},{"id":3,"subject":"History","date_of_creation":"Sun Feb 19 2023 1:10:41 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)","front":"What was the date of the gulf of Tonkin incident","back":"2 August 1964"},{"id":4,"subject":"Physics","date_of_creation":"Sun Feb 12 2023 12:21:50 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)","front":"What is Newton's Second Law of motion","back":"Force is equal to the rate of change of momentum (which equals to force multiplied by acceleration if mass is constant)"},{"id":5,"subject":"Physics","date_of_creation":"Tue Feb 14 2023 20:30:12 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)","front":"What is the equation for the moment of inertia of a rod about one of its ends","back":"1/3mL^2 where L is the length of the rod and m is the mass of the rod"},{"id":6,"subject":"Maths","front":"What can be said about the inverse of an orthogonal matrix","back":"The inverse is also an orthogonal matrix","date_of_creation":"Fri Mar 03 2023 15:00:00 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":7,"subject":"Maths","front":"What can be said about the inverse of an orthogonal matrix","back":"The inverse is also orthogonal","date_of_creation":"Fri Mar 03 2023 15:00:00 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":8,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is the equation relating acceleration, velocity, and radius in circular motion","back":"a = v^2/r","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 09:13:23 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":9,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is Kirchoff's first law","back":"The sum of all currents flowing into a junction is equal to the sum of all currents flowing out of a junction","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 09:15:05 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":10,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is Kirchoff's second law","back":"The sum of potential differences of the components is equal to 0 around any closed loop in a circuit","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 11:28:05 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":11,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is the equation relating power, voltage and current","back":"P = IV","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 11:32:15 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":12,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is the equation relating voltage, current and resistance","back":"V = IR","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 11:33:58 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":13,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is the SI unit for resistance","back":"ohms","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 11:36:03 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":14,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is the equation relating mass, distance between two objects and gravitational force","back":"F = Gm1m2/r^2","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 11:38:15 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":15,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is the value of g to 3 significant figures","back":"9.81ms^-2","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 11:44:23 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":16,"subject":"History","front":"When did the Korean war begin","back":"25 June 1970","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 12:18:31 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":17,"subject":"Chemistry","front":"What is Le Chatelier's principle","back":"If coniditions are changed in a dynamic equilibrium, the positon of the equilibrium shifts to counteract this change","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 12:21:54 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":18,"subject":"Maths","front":"What method would normally be used to integrate lnxdx","back":"Integration by parts","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 12:22:48 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":19,"subject":"Chemistry","front":"What is obtained when oxidising a primary alcohol under reflux","back":"A carboxylic acid","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 12:25:41 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":20,"subject":"Chemistry","front":"What is obtained when oxidising a primary alcohol under distillation","back":"An alkane","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 12:28:29 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":21,"subject":"Chemistry","front":"What is obtained when oxidising a secondary alochol under reflux","back":"A ketone","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 12:29:58 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":22,"subject":"Chemistry","front":"What kind of alcohols is difficult to oxidise","back":"Tertiary alcohols","date_of_creation":"Wed Mar 08 2023 12:31:31 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":23,"subject":"Physics","front":"What is the equation relating buoyancy force, density, gravitational field strength and volume","back":"Buoyancy force = density * graviational field strength * volumne","date_of_creation":"Thu Mar 09 2023 20:56:38 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)"},{"id":24,"subject":"History","front":"What date did the October Revolution happen","back":"6 November 1917 or 24 October 1917 in the Julian calendar"}]}